Oh, my friends, and welcome to exercise number 64, we are asked to write a function to find the size
of a LinkedIn list.
We have talked about this topic in the in the lectures before and we have seen them algorithm behind
it.
I want from you to watch that game from the lectures and try to write your own method, your own function
that find the size of a double the list.
And I am waiting your solutions in the comments below.
So post the video and think about it.
And welcome again.
So we will start making exercise, solving exercise number 64.
And by the way, I have created these methods and I put the complexity of every method.
OK.
So please go and check them.
You can check these methods.
OK.
No, this is exercise number 64.
I will create public static and find out earth size size.
And it took into the pretty metered note why we are passing in because this function returns the size
of doubling list and it have a counter.
This counter depends on the first method and the first known that from it, we will start counting.
So we should specify the start and the beginning of the linkage list and then we will start making and
counting and returning the size of this note.
So we need to pass through all the notes in order to determine the size of the link list.
I will create the counter equal to zero and.
Since I need to pass through all the elements, so I will use a while loop, so wide note here does
not equal to now, then make that count count plus plus increase count by one and no reference equal
to no dog next.
And this we are moving to the next note.
And by this, we are increasing the counter by one.
OK.
Return address that get account for the result.
By this, we can create a method that returns the count of the nodes and the size of the nodes of that
linkage list.
Let's test this.
I go down to the main main function and.
I will put here system that out, the footprint and size of the size of list is.
The althought size
or we can use size directly because it is static and they need to test the head of their link, at least
to start counting from.
Let's run and see.
We remember that this function return that you see the size of the list is is a three.
OK?
We have 99, two and four.
We have three notes and it's working perfect.
OK.
So thank you, guys.
I hope you benefit from our videos.
I need from you to make a favor for us and let us focus stars on Udemy to support us and make new videos
every week.
Thank.